https://transair.co.uk/privacy-policy

Search
X
UK +44 (0)1273 466000Order Before 15.00 for Same day Despatch!
Flight Cases
Headset and Cockpit Bag...
Fuel Testers and Gauges
Log Book & Licence Cove...
Pilot Sunglasses
Pilot Watches & Chronog...
Nordian ATPL Manuals
CATS ATPL Manuals (Cranfield Aviation Training)
CPL/ATPL Questions and Answers
ATPL Exam Resources (CAP's, GSPRM)
PPL(H) Study Packs
PPL (H) Studies and Reading
CPL/ATPL (H) Pilot Studies and Reading
Helicopter Type Rating Guides
Regulations (FAR-AIM)
Survival Accessories
Carbon Monoxide Detecto...
AeroShell Piston Oil
AeroShell Oil W 15W-50 AeroShell Oil 80 AeroShell Oil W80 AeroShell Oil W80 Plus AeroShell Oil 100 AeroShell Oil W100 AeroShell Oil W100 Plus AeroShell Oil W120 AeroShell Oil Sport PLUS 4 AeroShell Oil Diesel Ultra
Total Piston Oil
Total Aero DM 15W50 Total Aero D80 Total Aero D100 Total Aero D120 Total Aero 80 Total Aero 100 Total Aero 120 Total Aero XPD 80 Total Aero XPD 100 Total Aero DM 20W60
AeroShell Turbine Oil
AeroShell Turbine 2 AeroShell Turbine 3 AeroShell Turbine 308 AeroShell Turbine 390 AeroShell Turbine 500 AeroShell Turbine 555 AeroShell Turbine 560 Aeroshell Turbine 750 Aeroshell Turbine Ascender
Mobil Turbine Oil
Mobil Jet Oil II Mobil Jet Oil 254 Mobil Jet Oil 387
AeroShell Fluid
Aeroshell Fluid 2XN Aeroshell Fluid 3 Aeroshell Fluid 5M-A Aeroshell Fluid 12 Aeroshell Fluid 31 Aeroshell Fluid 41 Aeroshell Fluid 61 Aeroshell Fluid 602 Aeroshell Fluid S8350 Aeroshell Calibrating Fluid 2 Aeroshell Compound 07 Aeroshell Landing Gear Fluid Aeroshell Shock Strut Fluid
AeroShell Grease
Aeroshell Grease 6 Aeroshell Grease 7 Aeroshell Grease 14 Aeroshell Grease 22 Aeroshell Grease 33 Aeroshell Grease 64 Aeroshell Grease 58
AeroShell Smoke Oil Shell Spirax Shell Water Detector Camguard
Oil Accessories
Oil Funnels Fuel and Oil Containers Fuel and Oil Pumps Exterior Cleaners Interior Cleaners Maintenance Tools Drum Trolley Spill Kits
De-Icing Fluid Clearview Polish
XCP Professional
XCP Rust Blocker XCP One XCP Green One XCP Lubricate and Protect
LPS Aerospace
LPS Lubricants LPS 3 Rust Inhibitor LPS Degreasers LPS CFC Free Electro Contact Cleaner LPS Tapmatic #1 Gold Cutting Fluid
Arrow Solutions
Arrow Aircraft Cleaner Arrow Deep Clean Arrow Loxotane Arrow Loxotane Fast Arrow Loxotane XF Arrow FastKlean Arrow Shield Arrow Super Slaks Arrow Supersolve
Alglas
Ambersil
Ambersil Cleaning Ambersil Lubricants
Aero Sense ACF-50 Anti-Corrosion
3M Adhesives and Tapes
3M Adhesives and Fasteners 3M Applicators and Accessories 3M Scotch-Weld DP Series Adhesives 3M Scotch-Weld Spray Adhesives 3M Specialist Tapes
Aircraft and Airfield
Aircraft Maintenance
Aircraft Batteries Aircraft Oil Filters Aircraft Spark Plugs Brackett Aero Air Filters Aircraft Lighting Aircraft Tyres Fire Extinguishers Aircraft Cleaning and Care Red Box Aviation Products Maintenance Tool Kits Aircraft Screw Kits Aircraft Decals and Placards
Cleaning & Care
Aircraft Polish Airframe Cleaner Anti-Corrosion Products Cloths & Sponges Glass Display Cleaners Windshield Cleaner
Aircraft Accessories
Aircraft Logbooks Aircraft Static Wick Aircraft Chocks Aircraft Tow Bars Tie-Down Kits Fuel Testers and Gauges Pitot Covers and Control Locks Cockpit Dehumidifiers Cockpit Sun Visors Fire Extinguishers First Aid Kits Aircraft Checklists Carbon Monoxide Detectors Convenience and Sick Bags Cockpit Video Cameras Aircraft Tracking Aircraft Tugs Stall Horn Tester
Aircraft Instruments
Clocks and Timers Compasses RC Allen Falcon Gauge Mid-Continent Winter Instruments OAT Gauges
Aircraft Ground Power
Airfield Equipment
Aircraft Chocks Aircraft Tie-Down Kits Airfield Lighting Aircraft Tugs Marshalling Wands Ground Crew Equipment Windsocks Wind Speed Meters Aircraft Tow Bars Ground-Air Radios Refuelling Equipment
Avionics and GPS
Avionics
ADS-B Receivers Dynon Avionics ICOM Becker Avionics TQ Avionics Funke Talos Aeolus GPS Receivers for iPads Antennas Intercoms
Garmin
Garmin Aviation GPS Garmin GPS Accessories Garmin D2 GPS Watches Garmin iPad GPS Garmin VIRB Camera
ICOM
ICOM Airband Transceivers ICOM Accessories
Yaesu
Yaesu Airband Transceivers Yaesu Accessories
TL Elektronic
TL elektronic Flight Instruments
Bad Elf Comant Antenna Fitting Tools
Airband
Airband Receivers Airband Receiver Accessories
Collision Avoidance
Charts and Guides
Flight Guides
Pooleys Flight Guides Ireland VFR Flight Guide Italian Flight Guides South African Flight Guide Flight Guide Accessories Navtech IFR Jeppesen Student Route Manual
CAA 1:250 000 Charts CAA 1:500 000 Charts Rogers Data VFR Charts
European VFR Charts
Austrian VFR Chart Belgium VFR Chart Croatia VFR Chart Czech Republic VFR Chart Denmark VFR Charts Eastern Europe Chart European Aerodromes Charts France VFR Charts German Charts Greece and Balkans Chart Hungary VFR Charts Ireland VFR Charts Italian VFR Charts Malta VFR Chart Netherlands VFR Chart Norwegian VFR Charts Poland VFR Charts Portugal VFR Chart Slovakia VFR Chart Spanish VFR Charts Swedish VFR Charts Swiss VFR Chart
Navtech IFR Charts Jeppesen IFR Charts London Heli-Route Chart Pilots Atlas Europe/USA Chart Accessories
Flight Bags and Cases
Flight Bags Flight Cases Headset and Cockpit Bags Brightline Bags LightSpeed Bags Ditching Survival Bag Flight Case Accessories
Headsets and Helmets
Aviation Headsets
Bose A20 Aviation Headsets Bose ProFlight Series 2 Aviation Headsets Bose Headset Accessories David Clark Headsets David Clark Headset Accessories Lightspeed ZULU 3 Headset Peltor Headsets Pilot Communication Headsets Phonak Freecom Headsets Telex Airman Headsets Telex Headset Accessories Transair TA-200 Headset MicroAvionics Headsets Headset Adaptors and Cables Headset Accessories Sennheiser Accessories Aircraft Intercoms Leather and Cloth Helmets Peltor Ear Defenders
Aviation Helmets
MSA Pilot Helmets Microavionics Helmets Cloth and Leather Helmets David Clark Helmets
Pilot Supplies
SPECIAL OFFERS Transair SkyDemon Packs Rulers & Plotters Pilot Log Books
Electronic Flight Bag
iPad Kneeboards iPad Accessories iPad Mini Kneeboards iPad Mini Accessories Batteries Charging & Power Banks iPad Cooling Cases SkyDemon Packs
Kneeboards
Pilot Kneeboards Pilot Flightboards Design 4 Pilots Microlight and Glider Kneeboards Kneeboard Accessories
iPad Charging Fuel Testers and Gauges Log Book & Licence Covers Pilot Torches Design 4 Pilots Sportys Pilot Supplies Flight Outfitters
RAM Mounts
RAM Apple iPad Mini Mounts RAM Apple iPad Mounts RAM Aviation GPS Mounts RAM Universal Mounts & Holders RAM Tablet Holders RAM Handheld GPS Mounts RAM Arms and Mounts RAM Cup Holder Mounts RAM Mobile Phone Holders RAM Tough-Claw RAM Camera and Camcorder Mounts RAM iPad Air Mounts RAM Miscellaneous
Pilot Sunglasses
Ray-Ban Pilots Sunglasses Bigatmo Sunglasses Dirty Dog Sunglasses Randolph Aviator Sunglasses Rapid Eyewear Pilot Sunglasses REVO Sunglasses Serengeti Sunglasses
Pilot Watches & Chronographs
AVI-8 Watches Avionic Pilots Watches Citizen Pilots Watches Garmin D2 GPS Watches Stopwatches and Timers
Gifts for Pilots
Aircraft Models Aircraft Ties Pins Aviation Clocks Aviation Mugs and Coasters Aviation Novelties Boeing Gifts Calendars and Diaries Cockpit and Aircraft Posters Pilots Keyrings Pilots Licence Covers Wooden Display Propellers
Microlight and Gliding
Microlight Kneeboards and Logbooks Microlight Flight Computers Microlight Aircraft Compasses Microlight Strobes and Antennas
Weather Forecasting Batteries Aviation DVDs Clearance
General Interest Books
Aviation Stories Aviation at War Aviation Humour Haynes Aircraft Manuals
Pilot Training
PPL Flight Training
PPL Study Packs Air Pilot's Manuals Pooleys PPL Exam Preparation Books PPL Questions and Answers Private Pilot Studies and Reading PPL & LAPL Sylabi and Briefings PPL CBT/Training Software
CPL and ATPL Training
ATPL Study Packs CAE Oxford ATPL Manuals Bristol Ground School ATPL Manuals Nordian ATPL Manuals CATS ATPL Manuals (Cranfield Aviation Training) Jeppesen ATPL Manuals ATPL CBT/Training Software CPL/ATPL Studies and Readings Type Rating Study Guides CPL/ATPL Questions and Answers ATPL Exam Resources (CAP's, GSPRM)
Helicopter Training
PPL(H) Study Packs PPL (H) Studies and Reading CPL/ATPL (H) Pilot Studies and Reading Helicopter Type Rating Guides
FAA Flight Training
Regulations (FAR-AIM) Private Pilot Helicopter Pilot Instrument Rating Flight Instructor Commercial Pilot Airline Transport Pilot FAA Study Packs
Training Equipment
Flight Computers Rulers and Plotters IFR Hoods, Glasses and Instrument Covers Training Posters
Flight Simulation & CBT
Real Sim Gear Avionics Elite Flight Simulator Systems Flight Simulator Software Simulator Yokes and Pedals Simulator Panel Avionics Simulator Throttles Joysticks and Flightsticks Flight Simulator Add-ons Computer Based Training
Ratings & Differences
Instrument Flying Night Flying Multi Engine Flying Flight Instruction Tailwheel Flying Aerobatics Mountain & Bush Flying Float Plane Flying Glass Cockpit/GPS/Automation Aircraft Guides Turbine Aircraft
Aircraft Checklists
Piper Cessna Diamond Cirrus Robin Mooney Beechcraft Robinson QREF GPS Checklists
Pilots Further Reading
Additional Further Reading Aircraft Maintenance Aircraft Systems ASA Books Human Factors & Case Studies Interview Preparation Meterology
Gliding Microlight Flying
Pilot Clothing
Pilot Shirts Pilot Epaulettes Pilot Jumpers Pilot Jackets Flight Suits Pilots Flying Gloves
Pilot Uniforms
Pilots Shirts Uniform Airline Jackets Uniform Trousers Uniform Caps Uniform Ties Uniform Belts Pilots Uniform Braid
Helmets and Goggles Pilots Flying Boots Kids Flight Jackets Aviation T-Shirts Aviation Patches Novelty Aviation Ties Hi-Vis Clothing
Survival Equipment
Lifejackets Switlik Lifejackets Liferafts Switlik Life Rafts Survival Dry Suits Kannad ELT's PLB Devices Strong Parachutes Fire Extinguishers
SkyOx Oxygen Systems
SkyOx Aircraft Oxygen Systems SkyOx Oxygen Accessories
Survival Accessories Carbon Monoxide Detectors First Aid Kits
Home /
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
When you contact and/or place an order with Transair UK Ltd:
The information you provide (such as name, address, email address, phone number, credit/debit card details) will be processed and stored so that it is possible to process your order, contact you regarding your order, respond to your correspondence, advise, provide information and send invoices and receipts relating to service provision.
Your personal information will not be shared with any third party.
Basis for Processing your Personal Information
Whenever we process your personal information we must have a legal basis for doing so. The legal bases we rely on are:
Consent                                                 : You have told us you are happy for us to process your personal information for a specific purpose Legitimate Interest                              : The processing is necessary for us to conduct business, but not where our interests are overridden by your interests or rights Performance of a Contract                : We must process your personal information in order to be able to provide you with our products
Use of Personal Data
We may use the personal data that we hold in the following ways:
To process the transaction and provide you with products To personalise your shopping experience with Transair UK Ltd through relevant marketing and offers
Keeping Customers informed
Transair UK Ltd would like to keep past customers and subscribers to our Newsletter informed of great offers, ideas and product information including new releases. Where we have your consent or it is in our legitimate interest to do so we may do this via email and/or post.
Information Security
Transair UK Ltd takes great care to ensure the security of personal data. We make sure that your information is protected from unauthorised access, loss, manipulation, falsification, destruction or unauthorised disclosure. This is done through appropriate technical measures and relevant policies.
We will only keep your data for the purpose it was collected for and only for as long as is necessary, after which it will be deleted or shredded.
Our website uses a "cookie" which would be stored on your browser, this helps us to provide you with a better service. If for any reason you do not want us to do this, you can usually modify your browser to prevent this happening.
The personal information which we hold will be held securely in accordance with our internal security policy, the law and the Safebuy Web Trader Code.
Access to Information
You have the right to request access to the information we have on you. You can do this by contacting us by email at info@transair.co.uk or by post. You will be required to provide proof of identity.
Information Correction
If you believe that the information we have about you is incorrect, you may contact us so that we can update it and keep your data accurate.
Information Deletion
If you wish Transair UK Ltd to delete the information about you, please contact us. If you wish to decline marketing emails after consenting, you can use the unsubscribe button provided.
Right to Object
If you believe that your data is not being processed for the purpose it has been collected for, you may object by contacting us at info@transair.co.uk .
Rights Related to Automated Decision Making and Profiling
Transair UK Ltd does not use automated decision making or profiling of personal data.
Summary
In accordance with the law, we only collect a limited amount of information about you that is necessary for order processing, correspondence, information and service provision.  We do not use profiling, we do not sell or pass your data to third parties. We do not use your data for purposes other than those specified. We make sure your data is stored securely. We delete all information deemed to be no longer necessary. We constantly review our Privacy Policies to keep it up to date in protecting your data.
Complaints
If you have a complaint regarding the way your personal data has been processed you may make a complaint to ourselves in the first instance at info@transair.co.uk
Company Information
FAQs
Job Vacancies
Contact Us
Locations
About Transair
More from Transair
Privacy Policy
Stay Connected With Us
Sign Up to our Newsletter and Receive 5% off your Next Order!
Thank You For Signing Up To Our Newsletter
×
To receive 5% off your next order, please apply Coupon Code NEWS5 to your basket. Code valid until 30/11/20. Retail Customers only, cannot be used when purchasing Bose Headsets.
Close
Thank You For Signing Up To Our Newsletter
×
To receive 5% off your next order, please apply Coupon Code NEWS5 to your basket. Code valid until 30/11/20. Retail Customers only, cannot be used when purchasing Bose Headsets.
Close
Copyright © 2020 Transair (UK) Limited. All Rights Reserved.
Transair Flight Equipment, Brighton City Airport, Shoreham-by-Sea, West Sussex, BN43 5FF. England.
Registered in United Kingdom. Company Registration Number 2121497 VAT No: GB 438 8620 23
We use cookies to ensure that you receive the best experience possible whilst you use our website
Accept
